It's not how you play the game. It's how the game plays you.
Spy Game is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Tony Scott.
On the day of his retirement, a veteran CIA agent learns that his former protégé has been arrested in China, is sentenced to die
the next morning in Beijing, and that the CIA is considering letting that happen to avoid an international scandal.
Nathan Muir, played by Robert Redford.
Tom Bishop, played by Brad Pitt.
Elizabeth Hadley, played by Catherine McCormack.
Charles Harker, played by Stephen Dillane.
Troy Folger, played by Larry Bryggman.
Gladys Jennip, played by Marianne Jean-Baptiste.
Spy Game is a 2001 action thriller film directed by Tony Scott and starring Robert
Redford and Brad Pitt as CIA operatives during the last days of the Cold War.
The American–French–German–Japanese co-production grossed $62 million in the United States and $143 million
worldwide on a $115 million budget and received mostly positive reviews from film critics.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, palestinian-israeli conflict,
central intelligence agency (cia), china, espionage.
The tone is intense.